<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE preface PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">
<preface id="preface">
  <title>Preface</title>

  <sect1>
    <title>Conventions Used in This Book</title>

    <para>The following typographical conventions are used in this
    book:</para>

    <variablelist>
      <varlistentry>
        <term><emphasis>Italic</emphasis></term>

        <listitem>
          <para>Indicates new terms, URLs, email addresses, filenames, and
          file extensions.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><literal>Constant width</literal></term>

        <listitem>
          <para>Used for program listings, as well as within paragraphs to
          refer to program elements such as variable or function names,
          databases, data types, environment variables, statements, and
          keywords.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><userinput>Constant width bold</userinput></term>

        <listitem>
          <para>Shows commands or other text that should be typed literally by
          the user.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>

      <varlistentry>
        <term><replaceable>Constant width italic</replaceable></term>

        <listitem>
          <para>Shows text that should be replaced with user-supplied values
          or by values determined by context.</para>
        </listitem>
      </varlistentry>
    </variablelist>

    <tip>
      <para>This element signifies a tip or suggestion.</para>
    </tip>

    <note>
      <para>This element signifies a general note.</para>
    </note>

    <caution>
      <para>This element indicates a warning or caution.</para>
    </caution>
  </sect1>

  <sect1>
    <title>Using Code Examples</title>

    <remark>PROD: Please reach out to author to find out if they will be
    uploading code examples to oreilly.com or their own site (e.g., GitHub).
    If there is no code download, delete this whole section. If there is, when you email digidist with the link, let them know what you filled in for title_title (should be as close to book title as possible, i.e., learning_python_2e). This info will determine where digidist loads the files.</remark>

    <para>Supplemental material (code examples, exercises, etc.) is available
    for download at <ulink url="https://github.com/oreillymedia/title_title"></ulink>.</para>

    <para>This book is here to help you get your job done. In general, if
    example code is offered with this book, you may use it in your programs
    and documentation. You do not need to contact us for permission unless
    you’re reproducing a significant portion of the code. For example, writing
    a program that uses several chunks of code from this book does not require
    permission. Selling or distributing a CD-ROM of examples from Make:
    books does require permission. Answering a question by citing this book
    and quoting example code does not require permission. Incorporating a
    significant amount of example code from this book into your product’s
    documentation does require permission.</para>

    <para>We appreciate, but do not require, attribution. An attribution
    usually includes the title, author, publisher, and ISBN. For example:
    “<emphasis>Book Title</emphasis> by Some Author (O’Reilly). Copyright 2012
    Some Copyright Holder, 978-0-596-xxxx-x.”</para>

    <para>If you feel your use of code examples falls outside fair use or the
    permission given above, feel free to contact us at
    <email>bookpermissions@makermedia.com</email>.</para>
  </sect1>

  <sect1>
    <title>O'Reilly Safari</title>

    <note role="safarienabled">
      <para><ulink role="orm:hideurl:ital"
      url="http://oreilly.com/safari">Safari</ulink> (formerly Safari Books Online) is a membership-based training and reference platform for enterprise, government, educators, and individuals.</para>
    </note>

    <para>Members have access to thousands of books, training videos, Learning Paths, interactive tutorials, and curated playlists from over 250 publishers, including O’Reilly Media, Harvard Business Review, Prentice Hall Professional, Addison-Wesley Professional, Microsoft Press, Sams, Que, Peachpit Press, Adobe, Focal Press, Cisco Press, John Wiley &amp; Sons, Syngress, Morgan Kaufmann, IBM Redbooks, Packt, Adobe Press, FT Press, Apress, Manning, New Riders, McGraw-Hill, Jones &amp; Bartlett, and Course Technology, among others. </para>

    <para>For more information, please visit <ulink role="orm:hideurl"
    url="http://www.oreilly.com/safari">http://oreilly.com/safari</ulink>.</para>

     </sect1>

  <sect1>
    <title>How to Contact Us</title>

    <para>Please address comments and questions concerning this book to the
    publisher:</para>

    <simplelist type="vert">
  <member>Maker Media, Inc.</member>
  <member>1700 Montgomery Street, Suite 240</member>
  <member>San Francisco, CA 94111</member>
  <member>877-306-6253 (in the United States or Canada)</member>
  <member>707-639-1355 (international or local)</member>
    </simplelist>

    <para>We have a web page for this book, where we list errata, examples,
    and any additional information. You can access this page at <ulink
    url="http://www.oreilly.com/catalog/&lt;catalog page&gt;"></ulink>.</para>

    <remark>Don’t forget to update the &lt;url&gt; attribute, too.</remark>

    <para>Make: unites, inspires, informs, and entertains a growing community of resourceful people who undertake amazing projects in
    their backyards, basements, and garages. Make: celebrates your
    right to tweak, hack, and bend any technology to your will. The
    Make: audience continues to be a growing culture and community that believes in bettering ourselves, our environment, our
    educational system—our entire world. This is much more than
    an audience, it’s a worldwide movement that Make is leading we call it the Maker Movement.</para>

    <para>For more information about Make:, visit us online:</para>

<simplelist type="vert">
  <member>Make: magazine: <ulink url="http://makezine.com/magazine"></ulink></member>
  <member>Maker Faire: <ulink url="http://makerfaire.com"></ulink></member>
  <member>Makezine.com: <ulink url="http://makezine.com"></ulink></member>
  <member>Maker Shed: <ulink url="http://makershed.com"></ulink></member>
</simplelist>
    <para>To comment or ask technical questions about this book, send email to
    <email>bookquestions@oreilly.com</email>.</para>

  </sect1>

    <sect1>
    <title>Acknowledgments</title>
    <para>Fill in here</para>
  </sect1>

</preface>
